{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"63","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"64","question":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d41\u0d03\u0d16\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f "},{"q_number":"68","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"69","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"70","question":"\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"71","question":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"117","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d35\u0d21\u0d47\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"118","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d27\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d4b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d41"},{"q_number":"119","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d41"},{"q_number":"120","question":"'\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d46' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d16\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"121","question":"\u0d2d\u0d17\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24 \u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"122","question":"\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"123","question":"\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"124","question":"\u0d2f\u0d41.\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d39\u0d57\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"125","question":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d35\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d21\u0d4b.\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"126","question":"'\u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"129","question":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"130","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d"},{"q_number":"131","question":"\u0d1c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d41"},{"q_number":"132","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f (\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d48\u0d32\u0d7c,1973)"},{"q_number":"133","question":"\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3f.\u0d1c\u0d3f.\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e \u0d36\u0d30\u0d7a"},{"q_number":"134","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d47\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7c \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"135","question":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d47\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d7b ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d7c.\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"364","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e - \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f ?","answer":":\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"365","question":"\u0d09\u0d2a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d\u200c \u0d39\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"366","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d28\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"367","question":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d28\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"368","question":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d05\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d28\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e"},{"q_number":"369","question":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d CEO :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"370","question":"\u0d38\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d : ","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d1c\u0d17\u0d26\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d16\u0d47\u0d39\u0d7c (44\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f )"},{"q_number":"371","question":"\u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d :","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d7e \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f (14\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f )"},{"q_number":"372","question":"\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d :","answer":"\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c (2017 \u0d1c\u0d42\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 )"},{"q_number":"373","question":"\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7c :","answer":"\u0d09\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d7d (24\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f )"},{"q_number":"374","question":"\u0d15\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c \u0d13\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d : ","answer":"\u0d36\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e"},{"q_number":"375","question":"\u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"Dr.\u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d7c \u0d2c\u0d38\u0d41"},{"q_number":"376","question":"ISRO \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"Dr.\u0d0e \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d7a \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"377","question":"UPAC \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ","answer":"\u0d21\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c \u0d06\u0d7c . \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"378","question":"UGC \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d47\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u200c"},{"q_number":"379","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7c :","answer":"\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"380","question":"\u0d2e\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7c :","answer":"\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d26\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"381","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c :","answer":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"382","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d21\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c : ","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d41\u0d30\u0d48"},{"q_number":"383","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d\u200c \u0d39\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"384","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d21\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"385","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d17\u0d41\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u200c"},{"q_number":"386","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d :","answer":"NILL"},{"q_number":"387","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d2d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d : ","answer":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30"},{"q_number":"388","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d31\u0d7d :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d41\u0d02\u0d37\u0d46\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d37\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"389","question":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7c :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d48\u0d32\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"390","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7c :","answer":"\u0d39\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d7d \u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 (7\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f )"},{"q_number":"391","question":"\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a : ","answer":"\u0d32\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d32\u0d02"},{"q_number":"392","question":"\u0d2e\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ","answer":"MR. \u0d28\u0d38\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"393","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d08\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"394","question":"\u0d37\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e"},{"q_number":"395","question":"\u0d37\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7c \u0d12\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d7a"},{"q_number":"396","question":"14\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d48 \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c\u0d21\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"397","question":"21 \u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d2c\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d40\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d57\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"398","question":"VSSC \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"DR.\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"399","question":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d7bc\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d39\u0d4d\u200c\u0d32\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"400","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"401","question":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d\u200c \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41"},{"q_number":"402","question":"\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d47 \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d0e \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"403","question":"TRAI \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b :","answer":"\u0d06\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e"},{"q_number":"404","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d21\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d46\u0d35\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b : ","answer":"\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"405","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c : ","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u200c \u0d24\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"406","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c :","answer":"\u0d36\u0d47\u0d16\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"881","question":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d40\u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d36\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48"},{"q_number":"882","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48"},{"q_number":"883","question":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d35\u0d02","answer":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d25\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"884","question":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"885","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d30\u0d23\u0d36\u0d43\u0d02\u0d16\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d41\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d21\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d47\u0d37\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48"},{"q_number":"886","question":"\u0d21\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0b\u0d24\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d12\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02","answer":"\u0d32\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"887","question":"1981-\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f","answer":"\u0d38\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"888","question":"\u0d1c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48"},{"q_number":"889","question":"2008 \u0d28\u0d35\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d32\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d-\u0d07-\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d47\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d","answer":"\u0d05\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d38\u0d2c\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"890","question":"2008-\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"891","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e-\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d40 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d14\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d40 \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"892","question":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2d\u0d40\u0d37\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"893","question":"\u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"894","question":"\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d37\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"895","question":"2011-\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d21\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"896","question":"\u0d38\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u200c \u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d21\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"897","question":"\u0d38\u0d57\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d21\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d24\u0d3f","answer":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"898","question":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"899","question":"1901-\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d37\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d41\u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31"},{"q_number":"900","question":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e -\u0d15\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"901","question":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"902","question":"\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d02\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"903","question":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d. \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"1882"},{"q_number":"904","question":"1988-\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"905","question":"1995-\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d07\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02"},{"q_number":"906","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"907","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?","answer":"8"},{"q_number":"908","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ?","answer":"1928-56"},{"q_number":"909","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"910","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46"},{"q_number":"911","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?","answer":"1947 \u0d1c\u0d42\u0d32\u0d48 22"},{"q_number":"912","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d02 ?","answer":"3:2"},{"q_number":"913","question":" \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?","answer":"24"},{"q_number":"914","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a \u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"915","question":"\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d26\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d .\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"916","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d12\u0d21\u0d40\u0d37"},{"q_number":"917","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d46\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d39\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"918","question":"\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d43\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"919","question":"\u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 21"},{"q_number":"920","question":"\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1963"},{"q_number":"921","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"922","question":"1972 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d43\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d39\u0d02"},{"q_number":"923","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"924","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2b\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d ?","answer":"1991-92"},{"q_number":"925","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d43\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28 ?","answer":"4"},{"q_number":"926","question":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d35 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d40\u0d30\u0d25\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"927","question":"\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d43\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?","answer":"5"},{"q_number":"928","question":"\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d20\u0d02"},{"q_number":"929","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"930","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"2.42%"},{"q_number":"931","question":"\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"7"},{"q_number":"932","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"7"},{"q_number":"933","question":"\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37 \u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d30\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4b \u0d18\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"934","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"935","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d (8)"},{"q_number":"936","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"937","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?","answer":"9"},{"q_number":"938","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"939","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d48\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d ?","answer":"1906 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f 1"},{"q_number":"940","question":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02"},{"q_number":"941","question":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02","answer":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"942","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d40\u0d34\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?","answer":"1965 \u0d32\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"943","question":"\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41"},{"q_number":"944","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d16\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"945","question":"\u0d2e\u0d57\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"946","question":"\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"1600 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40."},{"q_number":"947","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"948","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41-\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"949","question":"\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"950","question":"\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"951","question":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"952","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f \u2013 \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26"},{"q_number":"953","question":"\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 ?","answer":"2525 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40"},{"q_number":"954","question":"\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17 \u2013 \u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26"}]},"code":"100"}